

# KIERAN VIEIRA

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

w: www.kieranvieira.com
SOCIAL —
twitter.com/kirovieira  in linkedin.com/in/kieran-vieira/
instagram.com/vieiraillustration
SKILLS —
Photoshop
HTML5
CSS
Pre-Processors
React.js
WordPress (CMS)
Communication
Problem Solving Problem Solving
Teamwork
Creativity
HOBBIES —

I am very interested in all forms of art Music | Movies | Photography | Illustration

CONTACT

e: kieranvieira@live.com

**t:** 1 289 697 2134

#### ABOUT

I have been doing Graphic Design for almost a decade now specializing in improving user experience. I have been focusing on Web Development for the past 3 years and am currently enrolled in Lambda School's Full Stack Web Development program where I've expanded my tech stack to include many modern technologies.

# **EDUCATION**

#### FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

Lambda School | California | 2018 - 2019

## AN MYER SECONDARY

Niagara Falls | 2013 - 2017

## EXPERIENCE

#### WEB DEVELOPER

Vieira Illustration | Freelance | 2016 - Present

I have been doing freelance Web Development for multiple companies and creators for a couple years now and have been improving my skills with every project. Visit the website for more information http://vieiraillustration.com

## **GRAPHIC DESIGNER**

Vieira Illustration | Freelance | 2015 - Present

I've done multiple freelance designs, business cards, and logos for some well-known local companies to help with branding and company reach using Google Analytics, Google Business, Google AdWords, and WordPress for social management.

## STORE MANAGER / PIZZA CHEF

G'z Pizza and Wings | Niagara Falls, Ontario | 2017 - December 2018 (Business Sold)

Managed in store day to day tasks such as stocking store, managing online ordering/party orders, ensuring quality of food, customer service, and opening/closing store. Provided detailed reports on business analytics to maintain quality for the customers and franchise.